<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FIT UP</string>
    <string name="app_bar">AB WHEEL</string>
    <string name="app_header">5 MACHINES TO HELP TONE YOUR ABS</string>

    <string name="sit_up_bench">Ab benches are one of the oldest types of fitness equipment that can be always found in gyms.
        The latest ones are adjustable which means we can increase or decrease the angle of the board.
        This way we can change the resistance.\n\n
        Besides sit ups we can do a wide variety ab exercises, for instance, crunches, leg raising and twists etc.
        It is a truly valuable tool to train the entire core. On the other hand the best models can be used for any decline workouts.\n\n
        It is important to buy a sit up machine which is long and wide enough for you to avoid strains and injuries.\n\n
        You should get one which can be adjusted in many levels in order to increase or decrease the resistance for your needs.
    </string>
    <string name="ab_wheel">This is another very powerful tool to train abdominal muscles plus shoulders, arms and back.
        An ab wheel allows us to perform an efficient core workout.\n\n We can stimulate the muscles when we roll out and in.
        Therefore, the abdominal muscles are continuously used.
        Using it for beginners is a bit hard at first, but with some practise you can get used to it.
        I think, it is the best equipment for lower and upper abs training.\n\n
        You can read more about the benefits of using ab roller here.
        Furthermore, they are rather affordable.

</string>
    <string name="pull_up_bar">Pull up bars are great to do several body weight exercises and it is especially beneficial for working the abs.
        There are various workouts we can do to train the abdominis and the obliques.
        Hanging leg and knee raises have helped me a lot to get a flat stomach.\n\n
        There are two types of equipment that you can get to perform these efficient moves at home, a Power tower or a simple doorway or mounted pull up bar.
        I think, towers are better since you can do several other types of bodyweight exercises.
</string>
    <string name="stability_ball">An exercise ball is not a well-known exercise equipment for abs, however,
        with the help of it we can do various efficient exercises.\n\n
        Since, we have to control do motion more, it helps to train abdominal muscles better.
        With the help  of it we can do common exercises such as sit ups and crunches more efficiently and safely.
    </string>
    <string name="roman_chair">If you want to get slim waist it is vital to train your lower back.
        Strong lower back is also crucial for various other exercises and helps to avoid pain as well.\n\n
        Besides the hyper extension move, you can do a few advanced core exercises with the help of a Roman chair.\n\n
        A big mistake of beginners is that they only focus on their abdominal muscles and neglect hair lower back.
        This leads to lower back pain, bad posture and increase the possibility of various lower body injuries.


</string>
</resources>

